naturalhealth365.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy

**  
NaturalHealth365.com takes your privacy seriously**.  Please take a moment to read the following and learn more about our privacy policy.

NaturalHealth365.com NEVER rents or sells email addresses to third parties.  We honor and respect the privacy of our website visitors and subscribers, and unlike many other social networking sites, we DO NOT share user details with advertisers.

NaturalHealth365.com honors all email unsubscribe requests and will make every attempt to honor the privacy of its subscribers, viewers and sponsors.

 **Privacy Policy**

LAST UPDATED: May 23, 2018 for GDPR Compliance.

This Website is operated by NaturalHealth365 (“we” or “us”). The privacy policy below discloses our practices regarding information collection and usage this Website, www.naturalhealth365.com and Related Media only (“Website”). This privacy policy does not apply to any other website or service provided by us, our affiliates, sponsors, parent or subsidiary companies, or clients, unless it appears on such website or service. By using and visiting our Website and by submitting your personal information to us, you agree and authorize us to use your personal information as set out in this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, you may not access or otherwise use the Website or service. In using and continuing to use this Website and any products or services offered on it, you are confirming your consent to the terms of this privacy policy.

 **What information do we collect**?

We do not collect personal information from you unless you voluntarily supply it to us. “Personal information” means information which identifies you as an individual, and may include your name, email address, or telephone number.

Generally, we collect personal and other information from you when you email us; register as NaturalHealth365 affiliate; place an order for a product, course, program or summit offered on the website; respond to a survey; opt-in to our digital mailing list; apply for employment; or contact us or fill out an online form. When you place an order on our Website, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, credit card information, mailing address or phone number, as appropriate for the transaction. You may, however, visit our Website anonymously.

We may automatically collect certain non-personal information about you when you visit the Website. “Non-personal information” may include, but is not limited to, the type of browser or device operating system you use, the website that linked you to our Website, the time you spend and the pages you view on the Website, and your IP address. We may also aggregate information collected from Website visitors, such as the number of users in a particular region or having particular characteristics.

 **How do we use your information**?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.),
  * To improve our Website and offerings (We continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.),
  * To improve customer service (Your information helps us to respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs.),
  * To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.),
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Website feature,
  * To add you to our and/or our affiliates’ mailing lists so that we or our affiliates may – jointly or independently – send you emails, including promotional emails, related to our respective products,
  * To operate the Website and provide you with information or services that you have requested,
  * To send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions,
  * To process and consider your affiliate registration, and/or
  * To process and consider your job application.

Non-personal or aggregate information may be shared with any number of parties, provided that such information shall not specifically identify you.

 **How do we protect your information**?

We take commercially reasonable measures to ensure the personal information you disclose to us is kept secure. However, due to the inherently open nature of the Internet, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide online. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive and credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, who are required to keep the information confidential.

 **Do we use cookies**?

Yes, we use cookies. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enable the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Cookies and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve personal information from your device without your knowledge. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about Website traffic and Website interaction so that we can offer better Website experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Website visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you want to stop or restrict the placement of cookies or clear any cookies that may already be on your computer or device, please refer to and adjust your web browser preferences accordingly. Further information on cookies is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features and functionality of our Website.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties**?

We do not sell to or trade your personal information with outside parties. We may send your personal to our parent, subsidiary or related companies, affiliates and trusted third parties to help us process your personal information for the purposes set out in this privacy policy. We may transfer your personal information to our parent, subsidiary or related companies, affiliates, and trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep such information confidential. We may also permit our vendors and subcontractors to access your personal information, but only in connection with performing services for us. They are not authorized by us to use your personal information for their own benefit.

We may also release your information when we believe release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or when we reasonably believe we are required by law or legal process to enforce our Website policies; protect the legal rights, property, or safety of NaturalHealth365 or others; or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual unlawful or otherwise prohibited activities, including, but not limited to, fraud, harassment or other violations of law or the policies of the Website.

We may disclose your personal information in connection with a bankruptcy proceeding or if we or any of our assets or divisions are the subject of a sale or similar corporate transaction, including without limitation a merger, acquisition or change of control. Non-personal information, as defined in this privacy policy, may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Where do we send your information**?

Our Website is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Website, you freely and specifically give us your consent to export your personal information to the USA and to store and use it in the USA as specified in this privacy policy. You understand that data stored in the USA may be subject to lawful requests by the courts or law enforcement authorities in the USA.

 **How long do we keep your information**?

If you provide us with personal information through the Website, we retain your information for as long as necessary for our business purposes. This may include, but is not limited to, retaining such information to comply with our legal obligations, resolving legal disputes, and enforcing our agreements. Even if we delete some or all your personal information, we may continue to retain and use aggregate or anonymous data previously collected and/or anonymize or aggregate your personal information. Please note that we are not liable for any disclosures of your data due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties.

 **Third-party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Website or link to third party websites. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We do not operate or endorse these third-party websites. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. This privacy policy does not apply to third-party websites. When you link away from our Website, you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to read the policies and terms of every website you visit.

We may also integrate social networking services into the Website. You understand that we do not control such services and are not liable for the manner in which they operate. While we may provide you with the ability to use such services in connection with our Website, we are doing so merely as an accommodation and, like you, we are relying upon those third-party services to operate properly and fairly.

You should be aware that information that you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your personal information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the personal information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent, except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy.

 **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Website, products and services are not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. All our services and products are directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If we are made aware that we have received information about a minor under the age of 13 or any other information in violation of our policy, we will use reasonable efforts to locate and remove that information from our records. If you are under 13 years old and wish to ask a question or use this Website in any way which requires you to submit your personal information, please ask your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.

 **Opt-out Rights**

To opt-out of any future promotional messages from us, you should send us a request to unsubscribe at info @ naturalhealth365.com. We will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. However, we are not responsible for removing your personal information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided with your information in accordance with this privacy policy or your consent.

As noted above, you may opt-out of or restrict the placement of cookies on your device or remove them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs are not effective on many mobile devices. However, on many mobile devices, application users may opt out of certain mobile ads via their device settings.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section, which establishes the requirements, agreements, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing your use of our Website.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We will post any changes to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted. If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically. Please look at the top of this page for the last updated date.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us by email at info @ naturalhealth365.com or by USPS mail addressed as follows:

NaturalHealth365  
4327 S Highway 27 #187  
Clermont, FL 34711
